<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manju Kuah</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manju Kuah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:58:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Education My name is Manju Kuah and I&amp;rsquo;m a senior undergraduate computer science major at Oregon State University. I am currently in the applied cybersecurity track for CS. After completing key computer science courses I now have 4 years experience in C/C++, Python, x86 Assembly and HTML/CSS/Javascript. Key cybersecurity courses I have completed include:
Network Security
 authentication protocols, group key establishment and management, trusted intermediaries, public key infrastructures, SSL/TLS, IPSec, firewalls and intrusion detection  Computer Networks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:58:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>###ORTSOC Infrastructure
This project was part of my senior capstone at Oregon State University.My team and I designed and implemented security infrastructure for The Oregon Research and Teaching Security Operations Center (ORTSOC). The ORTSOC is a learning SOC for students that provides security operations for small organizations that may not be able to afford the services of a well-known or established SOC. This infrastructure uses the Elastic Stack, nginx, wireguard, BIND9 and other components which create the foundation of the infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
